folksy.com 2010-06-28

# Welcome to Folksy :: Solder, sew, cast, knit, sculpt, cut, go!

## Privacy Policy

Folksy complies with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 when dealing with all data received from visitors to the site. We only hold the data necessary to offer services provided on our website namely to allow users of the service to buy and sell and also message one another. We also keep user data to allow us to contact you in the advent of account withdrawal or new passwords being provided. 

We only hold personal data for as long as necessary. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted from our files. If you delete your account then all your personal data will be deleted too.

For administrative reasons email subscription data may be passed to and stored securely with third party service providers located outside the EEA (European Economic Area). 

We regularly email news and information updates to those customers who have specifically subscribed to our email service. All subscription emails sent by us contain clear information on how to unsubscribe from our email service. 

**We never sell, rent or exchange mailing lists.**

We may however share commercial and technical data with our partners where a customer has accessed and used our website. This data would not be personal data but would be anonymised [for example the kind of data you see in "Google Analytics"].

In accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, we never send bulk unsolicited emails, (popularly known as Spam) to email addresses.

We may send emails to existing customers or prospective customers who have enquired or registered with us, regarding products or services directly provided by us.

All emails sent by us will be clearly marked as originating from us. All such emails will also include clear instructions on how unsubscribe from our email service and any future emails. Such instructions will either include a link to a page to unsubscribe or a valid email address to which you should reply, with “unsubscribe” as the email subject heading.

Our website uses "cookies" to track use and allow customers to purchase from our website. Please note that these cookies do not contain or pass any personal, confidential or financial information or any other information that could be used to identify individual visitors or customers purchasing from our website. Please note that you are free to refuse cookies. However, for purely technical reasons this may prevent you from purchasing from our website. This is because anonymous cookies are commonly used to keep track of the contents of customers’ shopping baskets or trolleys during the checkout process. This facility ensures that the items added to (or removed from) your basket are accurately stated when you go to pay.

We've tried to abide by the policies set out by the [Campaign for Plain English](http://www.plainenglish.co.uk/). If you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy please email us at get@folksy.co.uk

#### Featured Seller: deebeale

Beautiful, colourful Gocco screen printed images full of prettily folky images of nature and wildlife. Perfect artwork to brighten your space. [[more]](https://web.archive.org/users/deebeale)

##### Rated **positive** by **27** out of **27** people

Visit deebeale.

#### Your Basket

You have **0 items** in your basket, totalling **£0.00**.   
Checkout Now →

### Recently viewed items

  *
